Please. Let
me see the powers of the priesthood he
said. There is a tree in the middle of
a low the mountain. A perfect place.
I am playing hide and seek is
a very credible threat but of course it
is always stuck in the tree house caught
her eyes caught. In the country.
By enemies on the bars and the
Beast. There are roses on the track
in the sand and the coming in my name is
John on the fence across the way there's
a great big yellow pine
trees sing the song.
Makes.
Me. Wanna bes on the bars
of the beast and easy to
follow the.
Mars' concluded not to be able.
To drag all curly makes seven times this
month he come home swallows six seven
six watch was his birthday don't count
give me. Anything for breakfast to grow
a can a mug of no car
a yes boss. All sense
of fine morning or I'll
shoot you. Yet out here but in the
morning my. Eyes What are you doing up
there I can't this time it's my turn
let brothers think I began so.
I let em have at it.
Did you let me. See you look so.
You got.
This thing since about the
way that Kansas City.
Now balls there is one
old pensioner I wished.
Bunny. Knew where I'd seen his face
before time or you just been around town
a couple years all you have no milk
of human kindness. Ornament to
a clinic warning Bonnie you see you're
a good there are values that are
contrary to what you may hear me.
Livered Believe me I go.
Well then
a mechanic. They go through
all that fog yes or.
Drive
a bunch of stoners. That. A lot
of make Douglas happy mining
is progress with land speed What are we
going to do. I don't know what you're going
to do ban me I do nothing two hundred
family order of beef a week for
a family they last two years that can be
a sizeable number I got twenty head one
of any other brand on the Mesa Verde I'm
not hauling some of us haven't got all the
money in the world some of us sane old
and tired and feel like being put upon you
interest me than go on. The first time I
find one of our hides when our brand hung
on one of them settlers fences I aim to
kill me
a Power Boy. You do what you want
McClintock. Do what we want. Fellows
my age generally call me G.W.
Or my plan take youngsters
call me Mr McClintock. All
right Mr McClintock not because I'm afraid
I'm in the Big East out of this country
and I reckon if I let
my car. Around now G.W.
. Happen I want to spread. I made him
a full practice say the doc gave me the
long face you want and also First on the
search for the states don't force. The
settlers get burned out there will be
a lot of harnesses countries to while that
we. Will Go On the in the territories
some more with
a lot of political appointees run and then
according to what they learned then some
college where they think
the towels are something
a milf Indians or some in front of
a cigar store. And lookin two year
old young man I'll do what I can.
Money over the house once in
a while right out of you and.
You never had to be just fine.
It's a nice morning in
a bus everybody's And I don't know their
own opinion like that again it's that
material. But
a thousand head after they're banging on.
And out of battle like the ship sailed
out of the North range.
Setting everyone with
a plan a Bible not the slightest idea of
a frame just. Drag Oh. Right that hog like
yesterday I mean so much change.
oh Oh
. I'm
a critic you'll be able planned homestead
and farm the Mesa Verde Yes sir the
government give us each honored sixty acres
government never gave anybody anything
some years back a lot like you came in at
a pretty good first year good summer easy
winter but the next year the last train
was in February and by June even the
jackrabbits had sense enough to get off the
mesa folks do you know who that is that's
a book plant. George Washington but
twenty I told him that Douglas he
controls the water rights on
two hundred square miles over
a and you know that lumber you got
at Cape Midland cut by his lovers
and melted his mails Douglas
I come close to killing you
a couple of times when we were
younger saddens me I didn't kid you
a badge you know I'm an old all lad Oh and
mines too I forgot to mention them all
at any age begrudge and poor people
a measly majorly one hundred sixty acres
that right Mr McLean do begrudge us
a little freedom and there is no such thing
as free land you make these homesteads
go you'll of earned every acre of it but
you just can't make them go on the Mesa
Verde God made that country for Buffalo
serves pretty well for cattle but I hate
stuff plow and even the government should
know all that you can't farm six thousand
feet above sea level and it's almost
a mechanic all troubled. About
you Douglas Douglas just plain
Douglas and you call him Mr
McClintock why. Well Douglas I
guess it's because he earned.
Mr clinic you know I'm
a good hand with cattle Mr McClellan like.
Oh you look now you come in with oh so
worse Oh yes sir but you don't have
a homestead and then sure you. Leave
when you. Are.
Really laced available anywhere. Well
believe me it's the best oh excuse
me please look around take
your time today go I've got
a thousand have and of cigars and twelve
of those hats for you over there. You know
lashing on the way some folks have
been different in that regard.
Why you don't like the morning I stole
some sticky and Larry's help you shot
tonight. Maybe you can forget about
standing up I mean
a problem. Well I were black
queens Bishop the king
for. You might be right just trying
to work this out when the letter came
a letter. For the Mr McClintock
warning Davy save me
a trip oh that had
a suit of clothes you picked out for my
birthday. Instead of this cowboy hat I'd
like to have this one if it's all right
with you sir all right with me Davy settle
it's like the kind of.
Main Street to start
a fight or I don't is that he had for all
I have to do is walk down the street and
some wiseacre will call me an Indian and
just like that the fights on Davey the
letter. And you are an Indian Yes I
know I'm in it but I'm also the fastest
runner in town I've got
a college education on the railroad Telegraph
does anybody say college man or hello
runner or hello telegraph or
no not even Howard knobhead
a the it's always let the N.
The and you go out of the store to the
ladies all right bookkeeper part time clerk
always nice little. Lady brought that
out here this morning asked for to be
taken out to the home ranch. And some lady
kind of tall with red hair called me Mr
Burnham by just as if she'd never seen me
before and as if that veil to cover the
face to keep me from recognizing
it I thought she was in the. Place
so. You better draw
a complex your case of the boss's favorite
part on. The fast place which reminds
me you better start tapering
off. Kathryn's and.
Crazy.
Part but that's all right said one.
Morning no idea that Sally
Barraud want. To live here
why aren't you out at the desk
helping out the bartender I see
a busy day give me the key to
a room seventeen one seventeen
and don't advertise it
yeah they're going to look like.
Their. Day off.
Day. What was he so
preoccupied about having you
know what he's back in to
Katie Yeah this social.
Life seventy Good morning I hope.
You're right but the summer clinic
I don't want to bother you I'm
sorry boy I told him no job.
The best.
Kathy.
I thought you'd want this.
First to get this far but overnight
upset your plans. That you
feel kind of silly I never received.
Because you have no sense of humor
why couldn't we set down in the hotel dining
room and talk about whatever it is you
want to talk about or why going to just
come out of that house and have everybody
know that we're meeting everybody you know
is and what's the difference where Mary
that is something she's not just.
You know the answer Katie. That isn't why
you sent for me. Let's get to the read
your leg. That's just the kind of remark
that's always India you can. Let us
open the discussion very well
our daughter is coming home in
a few days Rob she's
coming here it was just
a slip of the tongue that maybe refer to
this ugly Hamlet at home our daughter is
it so hard to say your name it's Becky
Rebecca I hate that. Anyway she's coming
home and I hope to persuade you to let it
live with me part of the time the capital
part of the time in New York and
of course Newport during the.
West Wing and then when. If he stays
he comes just as prudent as vulgar as
all of this kind of she goes your
way she'll be all show on no stay.
No go Kate. How I hate.
Yes the people in the world
are women. Have to be street.
Leading And that's the story. I saw your
picture in the paper the Governor's Ball
you were dancing with the
governor. I doubt. You have to be
a man first before you're
a gentleman he misses on both counts. A
shiny. Nope. Private.
You bet it is an expert I'm
telling you. It you may return Mr
leave me alone. Everybody
got one way or another.
About that job. I already told
you son I've got no need for
a farmer's or use for just one minute
Mr McClintock my father died last month
that's how come we lost our
homestead I've got a mother and
a little sister to feed I need
that job badly well gee. There's
a little more you're going to see my
home ranch foreman is over there.
Step down off of that chair it's Mr.
Dog leg. I've been punched many
a time in my life but never for
a hiring anybody. I know was. Never fake
before. Turn my stomach I suppose I should
have been great for you gave me the job
gave Well you got it all wrong
I don't give jobs I'll hire
a man you intend to give this man
a full day's work knowledgeable You mean
you're still hiring me Mr McLean Well yes
sir I mean I'll certainly deliver a
fair day's work for that I'll pay you
a very day's wage you won't give me
anything and I won't give you anything we
balled up our heads already only of the
settlers in Kemah done by the mine. That's
your plug yes or hop on him
and we'll go get your gear.
The next morning because
we're behind. Whole.
School.
And. I'm sure that all you find
people are interested in knowing just what
portion of this new land will be your to
hold. Jones and make Now Mr since you've
been more or less the leaders of our group
I'd like to have you come up in
a check big sack location. Hold it. Up
to that boy and give him thirty dollars
tell him the clinic pays he's writers
a month in advance the looks of
things that show you said to.
All my Mr Gray go. Well and what the way
all this visit from a
cattle baron I got such
a hang over of bureaucrats don't push me.
Say fellows are mending other Indians in
this homestead land friendly Indians my
following. Oh
a running buffalo All right back to
your own car on the way don't get drunk
together and it's going to be
a lot longer time because it's
against the law and you're with
a sheriff and I got my hands full they
came into town to meet the train the old
Indian chief to come home I heard they'd
been pardoned and all I wanted to arrive
in this week next week or next month or so
in the meantime I've got to do some with
them but I've cut out
a couple of your stairs to feed them otherwise
some of these settlers milk cows are
going to disappear That's right Madeleine.
Cut out whatever you and the Sheriff are
you going to catch the savages with all the
settlers your asking for trouble that's
a Douglas I already have plenty of trouble
please tell of my back but in Buffalo
bring your people over
the place live close.
Enough for. Any amount all of this nice to
see you believe that now all the twenty
years ago she was a mighty
handsome a. Kindly S.F.O.
You so still to me it's not for.
It was just like this I had a dead beat
a hole on the buffalo sharp fifty caliber
missed by as back neck trouble on the
fourth member. You come directly from him.
But you get this as my momma back to.
You thinking the same thing I am she's
a woman boss and she's got
a long high road. I really. Wish
that you did you could
see. This my mother.
Your mother and my sister pleased to meet
you Mr McLean take me Mr and my boss
here
a few choice words to say about your
best pitch. Yes Mr McClintock. They're
great.
Where you all can rubber of
a doubt about it why me I can't myself
I'm not talking about fire and yet I'm
retiring Yeah you've been Ruslan or as for
thirty years or going to put you out the
past year you'll have to do is give advice
be one of the family I tell myself I may
save you the trouble
she. You kill yourself.
I'll be one of the family I give you my
solemn word thank economy family I think to
like to get in fights yeah
a lot of time but I always pick all
I want to finally get to know us
by you look good I'm.
Good i hope everything is satisfactory
this is such a big house it'll take me
a while to get used to things please don't
hesitate to tell me if anything is wrong
I know BUSH Yes So. I just find
everything on my side my. Best apple
pie over at Hurley's right ma'am it is
believed that last but so we celebrate with
the great poet I mean everybody this OK
you want to do yes OK or which you
know or should you get because
you.
Don't seem possible one of them
could use all them close people
a civil tongue in your
unprepossessing face if
a man and I love my back it's pretty easy
yes ma'am by the way what does that word
unprepossessing me.
Was my own hand no current us not to help
the driver with my luggage I couldn't
trust anyone else in this house to
do anything correctly live each
command surely Yes Well McClure are you
moving back again yes but nothing is
changing except my place of residence. And
I'd be willing to put up with savages
rather than be denied the company of my
daughter and I'm proving that by moving in
here Mr clinic since it's my first day
would you excuse me if I go ahead OK
either and this is their war on
join the outfit please ma'am.
Well how refreshing a polite young
man here where did he come from he's
a farmer Oh you don't go home great
welcome home what on earth are
you doing in that idiotic looking out for
it I don't care call me Kate that's my
button and suit on but one for the books
and I'm sorry coconut cake kind of slipped
up from the times I remembered
you as being nice big. Oh.
You're going to stand there with that stupid
look on your face while the hired help
insult your wife he's just ignorant he
doesn't know any better than to tell the
truth and I can't help this stupid Look
I started acquiring it as you gained in
social prominence Mrs Macleod Were
you want I should. Put them in the
master bedroom. Yes
but most of Mr McClintock swings into one
other room back up the stairs would be
best so that he can't wake up the entire
owls whole period that just before
daybreak just man. Oh excuse
me here's your cigars Mr McClintock
I am Mrs McClinton gave me pleasure
this is the cook this lady does
a concert for us this is war on Mrs
Markland. Do very pleased to meet you Mrs
McClinton very pleased I guess is the I
just came to work here to day and I guess I
jumped to the conclusion that this was
a bachelor's household. It
is and then again it isn't
I will explain so everything will
be quite clear Mrs Wallace this is.
Mrs Barton. It has been
a bachelor's household for quite some time.
And it will be again just as soon as I
am out of here which would be as quickly
as I can make arrangements to take my
daughter back east with me. You see
she's coming home from school in
a few days and then we'll be off together
and you can return to conducting yourself
as you consider proper in
a bachelor's household can you shut up.
Until then I am mistress in this house
and I will give the orders. When I'm going
to say goodbye to meet you I say not
involving no one hopes
to tell you no and G.W.
As soon as my things are put away I want
to talk to you about Rebecca Yes My plans
that day. Or. To talk not
to be broadened and on
but. Hard to manage.
Where You Think You Can
I just remembered I got
a date but you said you want to have
a talk I heard. Naming
them baby I'm at the max
you. Say Mr Mack what
is unprepossessing me. I was called once
lamb looked it up in the dictionary
it's best you don't know what
it means thank you you have.
A. Lot of that I want yes what you want
to lie down tell it's true you wouldn't
expect that from you anyway. First I have
to look through the gong goes Barnum is
last bridge you see a yellow streak about
a foot but I'd run down his back on
Mr McClintock He ain't afraid No
I want to start that.
Right help this man was that he took off
a little I told him I wanted to talk to
us grandma we stand right over here when
you said it not stand a rock on us prospects
when you walk up to harsh grab a hunk
a main stepped up on him and some spark
where did he go. Last time I saw him he's
going he's but you know him he's
lobby go north south or west get me
a catch Yes ma'am but But what Or
maybe you shouldn't follow him
and maybe where he's going into what does
that mean that we should be in the Senate
just get the carriage was.
What happened to Bruce
Bruce she chewed up she wants to go to
town but Mr McClintock never said anything
to me about look young fella I'm not right
I'm the ramrod around this place you
better start give me
a yes or you can get the roof of this
house pulled down on your Yes sir.
I've got it OK OK. Hello
honey how is every day oh fine fine
Mr McClintock. I got you next time.
You. Be back they miss you.
Leave. Even if you don't take
the wrong move so I chose
a problem Queens and then just.
Plain. Old. I
thought I was doing back Camille. Here on.
This McLay. Actually
it can be reached bottom
and then in the game
a chance. So it would give me the
test of time. I have nothing to
do. Just remember attempt.
To.
Capture an idea you're going Mr McLean
talk I told you I wanted to talk to you
know could I get your glass of sherry
CATHERINE Oh thank you Mr Burton Valmai could
you see I came into town behind
our runaway team. Never cut the
horses that young man whose mother pretends
to be your cook Katherine your Why
thank you Mr I'm gone.
Now Mr McLean talk we have an awful lot to
talk over first thing I learned about in
the in-fighting was to wait for daylight
and what is our conversation got to do
with Indian fighting Indian fighting
is good experience for our time the
conversations all it all boys. It
is charitable it's replenished we
had quite
a ride out here so I finally got the team
settle down. I know it's your move I just
can't look here you're not going to sit
here all night long to pay checks when the
matter of our daughter remains on settled
I am going to remain here and play chess
no matter of our daughter is settled she
stays on such stuff Catherine your hair
oh it is
a mess after that all fall rot you know
it's just that I haven't seen you for
a long time and it seems to me
the last time I saw you was
a little dark no. It's
a funny thing that Dexter man's memory will
play. Mr I think that you've completely
lost your my. Think your hair I have not.
Had the money. Certainly don't
want to put myself in the face of
a full blown problems that
you seem to prefer take it
fell it oh.
Warning. From the still have all
night when time never quits.
BIRNBAUM pastor decides the game is over
you got me no Mr Berndt I still got
a good game Oh you played chess. They got.
Pretty good fer. Looks like I want
to have to command always to get
a game. Remember I'm
a bad loser. German.
Morning.
Cup of coffee. Please thanks Jane.
You're welcome. Any screen can cause
a. Good all condensed milk.
That reminds me. I was cleaning out my
desk the other day I found something I
wanted to return to.
This.
Metal remember. From the president
of the United States of America.
First Sergeant Michael actually killing
the bravery above and beyond the call of
duty.
Reminds me of the first time I ever saw
you. Was over seventeen years ago. I walked
into my store not much bigger than the
bundle you will carry. And in the bundle was
the most beautiful baby I have
a SIL. Who she hungry. Walked
all the way from superstition
creek. Just to trade me that medal for
a case again. G.W.
Was off somewhere as usual
fighting in the. Sharon.
Chair All right what have you seen
this year already have oh why
did I look like burn Bob stop
and maybe somebody here know.
So there you are just I told you you are
headed for trouble. Trouble I want to know
all by who was authority you met that was
and stay in town know savagest are wards
of the government and I am the representative
and I will share of Lord that he
could put them up down with that place.
Because the town's named after him he
thinks he owns it well you check the books
in the recorder's office and you'll find
I do own
a fair piece of it. A guard if you knew
anything about Indians you'd know that
they're doing their level best to put
up with our so called but Neville and
patronage in spite of the net income that
have been put in charge of it and in this
need my permission to leave the reservation
always chiefs have been giving orders
all their lives it's pretty hard for them
to understand that they have to hold up
their hand like a schoolboy in
a classroom the law is very clear I told
you you get no satisfaction from these
people well get the girl back girl the
girl in dance kit but don't worry
I are the settlers and sat down to rounding
up those red devils What is this about
a girl Billy Jones one of the settlers
daughters and kidnapper that's ridiculous
and you turn loose
a lot of farmers with shotguns I certainly
did your insane Let's go share.
Mr Dunn. Which you claim might just I hate
to agree with you about it and when you
have the means to do it you're
still an hysterical fool who.
Really got worried maybe Katie shot your
not yet Draco but it took risk trying to.
Think it was on the list
All right go to the war.
On drugs I'm just. Really.
Think you would. When you stop
showing off again this was
the first. Bird seed head or
a little bird. OK.
Let's go.
Just where do you think you are going don't
use that rain last time I said with me
.
Or boys mind up the
procedure. By both your.
I don't like in the clinic I don't like
it one bit why don't you like that when
either going to end your.
Funny voice. Oh that. Was so
mixed up the whole place you want to
wear a big hole in your. Lawn is G.W.
Going to look at Chee chalk a push
him around and she checker has
a sawed off shotgun. How do you know she
didn't wander off some place or meet some
feller sorry. I didn't raise my girl right
but she'd wonder off on what was some
There's a lot of things I'm not
saying to you Mr while you've got
a shotgun in my middle but how
do you know this Indian had
a thing to do with it he's
gone I mean she she's gone.
There. Is nothing funny
or you bring young damn took me by
sunrise run on the forest wandered away
I've been going over. She's telling the
truth Mr McLean if we were doing nothing
but let's not important right. Thing is it
you don't draw that hog like you're this
will be worse and Dodge City on Saturday
night you're going back and I can. I don't
come to you later. On with this never no
harm has been done young man here is one
of the nicest boys in the territory so
just put down that shotgun I'll let you go
forward Mike. We'll. All see
just
a little excitement I know I know I'm going
to use good judgment I haven't lost my
temper in forty years
but Pilgrim You caused
a lot of trouble it's morning must have
got somebody killed and somebody out I've
got to and I'm out but I
won't I will die well I.
Think you think you.
Know Mark.
I said I Do you.
Think You Are high I'll tell why.
Q.
A.
Thank you.
For this surely.
Let's look
like you. Like
to. Thank you thank you.
Let. ME
THANK YOU THANK YOU.
Ily. You.
Know here we.
I know. Well you know me thank you.
Very much. For have insight.
Oh great oh you never talk to. Your.
Kind if I make you lose your picture you
either face because you're out of camera
live this morning. Say
yes but you could be
a big help to one another like what may
I ask Well we could wash the mud off of
each other we used to have quite a good
time he was doing it sort of there are
a lot of things we use to be my style.
If you like what are you talking about
I mean divorce she still wanted you
yeah some women are funny she thought I
walk out on your side after the fact you
come home she slams of the one your face
divorce been is that what you get when you
pay
a woman enough to live with you. About
it some women know to be worth it you
know if we had any moral character we
wouldn't be standing here covered with mud
breaking when we should be
washing she'd be great go.
No armies this fish. Thank you Draco.
Morning Mrs Warren morning Mr Mix and
breakfast for the boss if that's the way you
wanted the rest of
a letter. One
post a T. O.
Most likely browned and on.
Why Mrs McClintic you have
a black guy I do. All
pole and bake he's coming on
to me it's not all there's
a little something we better get settled
there are no men listening now so we can
be ourselves Oh sure I let you get away
with all that guff the other night but now
that we're alone when I pick up the hired
help I'll ask. You know you could wind up
with two black eyes what
a hole I realize you had to put on that
big guy we always have to just before we
get ready to forgive them generally for
something they haven't done. But you and I
both know that's just to keep you from
getting the idea they run saying. My plan to
give you that like on the old.
Nobody game actually made
a what. Was
a big mistake. I.
Was. Going oh.
Oh oh. I guess I'm going to have
a go and you say. Oh. I
wasn't sure you'd be oh I've
been here
a few days at the bank your fortune
three of the most beautiful dress. Oh
you did you bring your own company brazen
sure you did. A moustache cup and when
you get me British Palomino pull me that
I reply to show OK and ground time.
Oh. Well you did Mr Douglas
this job oh Mr Douglas has
a fat had an accident. I
brought you all whole shipment
electoral sticks but now that I've seen
how much you've grown I think we better
exchange it for a couple of bucks
a dress good day. The mayor was going
to be here but he had to go to the
territorial capital on a host F.
Matter but I'm going to give it speech
bad eggs but I don't really have
automatic I'm sure that he can find
a bill of sale for the
horse because I. Ladies
and gentlemen we are here to welcome
the fairest. One of my doing.
We're here to welcome back the prettiest
girl that was ever born in McClintic or in
any part of the territory.
Yeah that's right. The
old neighborhood upright
so I like the men here I've had my scalp
a long time and I aim to keep it. Going
well you know I've got it all right.
And now she's come back to God of the pink
tail but there Freckles was still on the
prettiest face that was
ever born in McClintic.
Maybe that's too much. That's
true the government could turn.
Never forget. G. W.
. I Want To Miss Chester one hundred
fourteen course they weren't very
many. Came past the house at
a high low. Problem on the doorstep you
do remember them good old days don't you
cage.
My friends.
Also blood brothers never
get that oh. Still if they
lied when it comes on the writing I wouldn't
have to worry. That it was remembered
by. Return with news people have trouble.
You see I learned good
English now be. Learned in
a white man's jail. But we would
have you talk our course.
I understand the governor I'm
afraid the Pres. Yes Tom
I'll translate your wishes Mr McClintock.
Could I impose on you to use your command
to tell the Shiva the Comanches and
he speaks English very well. Oh well
your people will have to follow my instructions
to the letter it is the law of the
land. We're not just America.
For heaven's sakes.
But I hear. When I see that bad day
do you get that first big yes.
No warning system I'm talking to strangers
you know three clicks I'm very.
Very goal. Now of what you've
done baby this endeavor
and warm he works for you papa there is
a mistake in my planet those are my things
YES MAN Oh I don't know when you are
Miss Becky but do you mean. All I mean you
look so much like your mother were even
prettier Oh Mr Warren not as
much prettier than I am many
a fight started for just
a few. Weeks at cherry pie for dinner
I'm not cooking no worries now.
Yes Miss Becky you remembered you
need Douglas mama Carse House College
valedictorian ninety five Congratulations
Oh Mr This is Douglas we will see you at
the party of course old dear life here
will be pretty hard to keep young man away
yes. Yes all right he got
you you remember Young Jr.
Oh yes Like Father Like Son Oh I miss
him I hope you don't think I'm being
preceptress in asking for the honor of
calling on Mr Baca last year is as you
yourself THANK YOU SIR G.
Now I'm going to get fired.
Thank you thank you.
Yeah yeah yeah I was like father like son.
He mean if you. Come on to grammar
proud frankly called me I'm even going
to come home one of the. Little.
I know you are doing it so it's all this
makes me think. Yes When you're finished
there go over and help Draco
with the beer cake yes.
Could you give it to me
a minute. I
certainly was surprised to hear you went
to college why. I don't know Junior just
produce a good college for a backwater
place like Indiana you didn't do
a could you do this I can't reach it. I
wanted to finish college lack of funds
my father got second to come
out West so he took out
a homestead. You know your Mom shook you
it's too bad you didn't inherit her eyes.
Well you've been lucky
if you didn't hear it
a few things from your
father. For instance.
It was common sense for instance common
sense you don't see him being fooled by
some dude like Junior
Douglas Junior is not
a dude he's lefty. You speak
the woman's touch. The sides
think I'll enter it college sport
glee club very strenuous so.
I have no intention of harming you.
Ladies Oh look lovely
Catherine. And this is
a real fine party I thank you of course
we have given hi to everybody. And I.
Love you just once my. Oh thank you
Miss you are I guess I'll live to be
a good host my want to make
you and your sister like you.
I.
Don't do what I told you to do. CATHERINE
Do you told Craig old this great going.
Right oh well. Yes. This junior is
going to bring you folks Tom De
Lay to stop the car and dance steps
to pop I am directly from no you.
Give me away the limbs IMO but it's ten
a ten down funny. When I run
out of whiskey I can take on
a lot of them couple of those little.
You still got any ideas about asking my
sister to dance it off and we can do the
soul for us. I feel.
Just like you. I don't think it was so
fair and square. When you want to take
up where he left off if I did
you wouldn't find it so easy.
Oh we've had enough of this one you're
going to quit walking away just as soon as
we're out of sight of the party the lesson
I learned back home don't fight for our
women over our site now so we are.
Known Garrity someone should do
something about it. You're right.
Absolutely right.
We were I knew them. All right Mr
McLaren. Pretty fancy fighting
country boy two years of to do Mr clinic
on the parks and. I never thought any
farmer could well make. Sure it
is. Cleaned up getting some water
to.
Get yourself cleaned
up so as that girl for
a day and who. Know.
How to do this would. GO BUT
FIRST never try to work.
Predicted and in almost all year the young
farmer bought it with my nephew and
on phone where I say young man down well
I'm no farmer but if you're young Ben's
uncle yes I whipped him and you're
intruding but centered me but man oh
so he is and soft and me well and I got
another reason for wanting the sad on again
I am thrashing my nephew young band are you
can't get mixed up in these youngsters
quarrel family honor I can have
set up a farmer went to say
a G R twice his size don't let that bother
Mr McClintock Mr Fauntleroy insists I'll
just have to teach him the same lesson.
Sank.
Sorry I'm prouder. Of it I have to do
that young gotta know I've failed and
not yet. And I'm just what I
mean that isn't all now wait
a minute. Father I we're
going to make this
a fair fight who's We are cordially argy
dad you know be none of this I don't want
to do that gee that you wouldn't do the
island is and they have I don't want you
kickin father Roy in the knees he didn't
and I started playing and none of this no
twisting. To me is all you are. You.
Know what. You are you
proud are. Low right
this Indian nation will stop stepping all
over me and make you oh yeah yeah you're
just not. That I want you to know that boy
brought me up by well I'm glad to hear
that. My uncle. Walk or go I
want to you have been going out
while didn't bother anybody no bother I
think we'd better join the lady before they
get curious. Pomeroy That's why
I'm off or don't you go Jake.
You think tincture of our Nicko would
help could be used to help you
gentleman through the medicine cabinet.
They. Were one of the scared to go.
To War.
Might add
a. Little. To get you out store like
something I have to get straight in my mind
you know. What. Mama.
Why did you number stop living
together Daddy. But you said to me
aren't you going to answer me you know.
Is sort of my business I think I don't.
Is another woman usually is at your age
always you know was HUGE your business
is more. Becky I don't want to start laying
the law down your first day back home
but I'll have no more such talk first time
I ever saw Mrs Warren was last week she
has a job here at which she's
very good and I hope you'll have
a good manners to not pry and
other people's business.
Your mother's and mine pretty good shot
at me. So I can understand you travel
down the Gulf and so well so
Captain and petulant you learned
a lot of words baggies Becky was to God
that touches some meanings they were only
about six months old one Your mother
stayed along with in the side hut and the
right foot of snow while I moved her three
hundred miles south to try and save it
saved about half of it
you were a little more
a year old at the time of the great
Comanche raids we stood off by
a hundred Plains Indians for nine
days petulant back I think you better
go on home see that saying get the birds.
Back gate. And we're.
Some mileage. It's not
a good plan as in you're going to have every
young buck west of the Missouri around
here trying to marry you. Mostly because
you're I handsome fella but partly because
I own everything in this country from
here to there I'll think you're going to
inherit it but you're not
going to leave most of it.
Well of the nation really for
a park or no lumber mill cut down
all the trees for houses with
a leaky roof. Nobody else killed all of
beaver for hats for Dodes or murder the
bubble over robes Well
I'm going to give you is
a five hundred cal spread on the upper
Green River and I may not seem like much
more than we your mother. Some folks
are going to say I'm doing all this
so I can sit up in the
hereafter and look down on
a park named after that I was disappointed
and you didn't want you to get all that
money but the real reason Becky is because
I love you and I want you and some
young man have what I had because all
the gold in the United States Treasury
all our harp music in heaven and
equal what happens between a man and
a woman and all I grow and
again I can't explain
it any better than.
Thank you. When years old and die and
you'll thank me for this. Program. So much
to learn about you.
Thinking about you in Rome.
Oh.
Well there all three of them rise out
of the carrier Oh. Well this is getting
rather nice Becky it's that time mother.
He brought this he must have intended to
use that holiday that is not well
if you really want to gosh I have
a plate you are just right for me.
To raise and I thought Oh oh.
They have what are you doing oh. Yeah I
just thought I'd get another cigar. But
you got one in your mouth into burning in
the tri. Plate of.
Your cute. Maybe. Softer
and. I want the whole relied on
today. Or just to run for.
Your. Oh no not that big and you know do
it the way to do it the plaza I know the
way sure Becky will you
sing with me. All right.
Good to hear oh. Oh you're playing like an
amateur. Call it an evening I'd like
to know where your mind is tonight.
Are. You glad you're back.
On Me. Any.
I'm sure. Honey. I won't melt and you.
May to.
This day play.
So good I kind of hate to break this up but
we're going to have that Indian hearing
tomorrow morning said about our conversation
earlier this evening I believe I'd
better apologize. Yes and I've been
thinking it over and when I called you
reactionary and that's merely my generation's
term for your generation then nothing
personal say oh really. Good night. Good
night Mr McClintock good
night to come again night.
Was reactionary me me guess. Anyone the
one of the cell of the Prophet was
a reactionary reactionaries
back and embrace when you sell
a beef cattle for six cents
a pound on one of the. College boys. Every
morning viewers my economy and you wouldn't
walk off the preschool that put them in
a fight. What can I do I'm just one
of her father's employees just
a hired hand around here every so
often day of. Strangest ideas.
Everybody works for somebody I work for
everybody in these United States that steps
into a butcher shop for a T.
Bone steak and you work for me it's
not much different. Guys it was
a terrible thing just happen. Junior's
horse ran away but what do you manage the
livery stable trying to get rid of horse
by the Rangers probably back in the stall
by now I think we could get Junior something
that he can ride what I'd rather do
daddy is Dr Jr home in our group it's
a lovely evening and I'm sure Uncle Draco
wouldn't mind driving. The kind of
manners don't keep me from saying just to
be polite I'll drive home Mr McClintock
you don't have to come
a specky I'll see that he gets home
safely I can take care of myself you got
yourself
a foot did you get curious Draco I'm
going now you got me right do. You
make. Me
eat this Becky somebody better tell me
what's the road you know I'm no run here I
take the wrong turn up again
and you know there isn't
a turn off between here
in town. This out with. A
gun I. Just.
Can't. Be your friend.
I am not so sure my entire life I said what
I said I'll stand by to the death sure
you got me show them it was.
Why my honor is at stake Well
no your honor absolutely he imputes my on
a few one of the many times he slandered
my honor he did I said what I said and
I'll stand by it to the death he. Showed
him well what is he admitting to call me
what even repeat the word I didn't necessarily
call you want anything but I said
what I said No I'll stand by it to the death
well just for the telly books what did
you say I said that any girl would permit
Amanda kisser before they were formally
engaged is
a trollop. I mean no hold on hold
on if you want my father if you
love me you'll shoot him well I'm
your father and I sure love you so.
You really got him. If he dies he'll
be the first man ever killed with
a blank cartridge use this to
start the races on the for
a. Writer who you would see
here poor dear you had me
shock cold blood didn't happen yelling
and told you what all what you need is
a good spanking have. Made me out of this.
I think I'll give you what you deserve
you. Know I told time before you don't
want just can't I'm just going to.
Be given half
a. The Soon he'll lose. Thank my daughter.
She only knew stood there while
that broke be how daughter she W.
What's happened to you in the last resort
of our show business you know that you've
always treated me like
a squat without subjecting dear sweet that
he did these cruel fall go very you know
women are always raising hell about one
thing when I see something else you're
really sorry about don't you think it's
about time you told me what but the burrow
under your saddle about me I don't
intend to stand here and hold
a midnight conversation
with an intoxicated man.
And I am not intoxicated.
Yet.
You want your sergeant. Big McClintock
we know you'll get those photos when
you don't really follow me.
Well Jake she W.
. Well
J W It's been
a long time not long enough
that's worked. Your husband is
a rude man yes but I know.
Well you know one day when fact Mr McClintock
is not running this hearing Sergeant
those Indians. Generally
think that. Their whole
want to come into town was
a lieutenant. This hearing is now in
session governor Caspar Hopper is
presiding like Eddie.
Government edict number eight.
As ordered to command you nation be
transferred from their present reservation to
Fort Sill because the government's
claim is filed by an Indian agent.
These chiefs after being
released from prison by
a kindly government. Doesn't incite
defiance among the tribe against.
It seems gentlemen that although some of
these chiefs speak English Puma is quite
at home in our language they have chosen
Mr McClintock to be the spokesman. For the
committee or rather I offer
this translation. To McClintock
the Comanches. We are an old people and
a proud people when the white man first
came on my house we were as many as the
grass is of the. Now we are
few but we are still proud
for of
a man lose his bride man of ideas nothing
you tell us now that if we will let you
send us away to this place called Fort
Sill you will feed us and care for us
let us tell you this it is
a Comanche law that no Chief every last
Thursday sees that the parts are full of
meat in the lodges of the widows
and orphans Comanche way of life.
That the white man calls
charity is a fine thing for
a way those in our friends but no lawyer
can accept it already does he is no longer
a man when he is no longer
a man he is nothing better off dead you
say to the Comanche you are widows and
orphans you are not man and we can actually
say we would rather be dead it will not
be remembered by when you kill us because
we are few now and have been but we will
fight and we will die.
Thank you. And I together the commands you
defy the government of the United States
yes you may gather that the Comanche defy
the United States government or at least
.
The order of the court. To be
incarcerated until such time as
a detachment of United States Cavalry
be made available to escort them in the
Comanche nation before.
This court adjourned.
Call McLin talk to our important.
People sway them have them give us
a few guns to make to fight worth while.
One last remember fight part of the march
. I almost wish I could arrange the film.
I did. Carry all.
The time changing.
Wow.
But oh well it's.
Funny. Already McClintic. Figured
you'd be belly down rules
well I've been doing some thinking drinkin
Bonnie is that boxcar still on the side
well sure but what I don't like you don't
you figure they need to get out there and
lead to carry on a wild goose chase
a Great White Father going to get no answer
you know early in the whole investigate
when they find out how that sidesaddle
governor's been messing things up those
Indians
a fair trial that's live ammunition in
that box car you know what happened to me
and get some guns in their hands somebody's
going to get hurt Wilma's word good
enough for you. We're going to go chill
the partners leave me out of this
clearly. Good night funny.
Good night Governor.
All I. We. ROSE.
Never.
Ever. Ever I.
K. J.
J. Chatter. Holy.
Cow I missed an expressway.
All right. This just
was. Relieved in
a. Way that for you Mr McLean. I want
to talk to you about something you
cited. Three hundred nine
times I think part three
times straight without
a miss record I suppose you can
appreciate what I wanted to sound steps
six inch brim fifty three feet gotta
be erected I'm sure is the reason I
am woman can't you hold
a glass still coarser
now. Down to my world
record. Down I had. Yesterday.
You. Are the governor
of our territory. The governor of the
territory don't you stick up for him this is
one you're
a fine woman Mrs one but you'll certainly
go down in my estimation if you stick up
for custard H.
Humphrey governor of this territory
don't mean to down that.
Big Eight from the governor a large
territory is a car. You know what
a college man. A college
a specimen that is so Morris lets the gent
to cut him out of them or now if all the
people in the world are put in one herd.
Comfort is when I would throw my rope back
. At him I would throw my
rope at. Natural born.
Another test ma'am owned.
By I don't mind if I do. It was one leg
although I didn't mean to be vulgar
man can't walk limp sorry. Selves
silly only a bird can walk on
a limb. You know my wife her name's Kate
she insists on being called Captain do you
know or of course in the clinic and that's
what I wanted to twelve she thinks that
cussed brick H.
From Ray is standing for her like a
bull buffalo at the first green of
a spring but what cupboard
is panning for is my money.
Don't make me feel like I'm drinking all
ma'am very well Mr McClintock If you
insist. Down the hatch.
Mr McClintock I have something
very important to say to you.
Very important. After wait all morning.
To do. The top. Thirty five.
Just.
As you are on. The assist you. Cast.
No idea what biology. I'm going to.
My mother. Going On Here now Catherine
are you going to believe what you
see or what I tell you. The same
Mrs McClintock hope you won't misunderstand
it's the first hundred women sitting on
his lap and I misunderstood number one
hundred one it's quite. Clear Doc I.
Just when I know exactly
what I want to see and.
I raise it up to talk to Mr. McClintock.
I want to tell him I was quitting
is the sheriff Lord has asked me
to marry him and. Congratulations.
I don't want to seem prudish but hand if
you are going to marry sheriff Lord it
seems to me that you're sitting
on the wrong man's lap.
But I have
a long talk about men in general. Why
go on.
Oh the get on. Well.
Wait
a minute ladies to like get to my breasts
and I'll get you up those stairs and sure
my name is George Washington mostly.
You made
a pretty Mrs was for it but not I
thought I read that let me out
Oh I see Brown somebody is your button
knob on my skull huge cage speaking
Katie why. Mrs Warner. You was there
when you bought it was there against ever
being what Katie's temper is room. For
a gold friend. My wife does
not understand we are.
Getting here and you've been
a big celebration of Y.A.Y.
.
I am sleeping in the den.
All right.
Already girl.
Yeah right yeah you will
be going to wheedle. Oh oh
oh. Come on getting on board
a body ready then number five
in Egypt thanks to. Anyone.
That I know you're ready Larry. Just
to make sure it is more you are
to present to you the girl over territory.
From free. Thank you. My friends I
am still dozens of this great territory
this is the ninth consecutive year it is
been my privilege and my pleasure to
inaugurate Democratic clothes of July
celebration all the presidents will
be the wild horse race. But before I
fire the shot to stop the
event I would like to say
a few modest words regarding
my stewardship of this.
Thank you thank
you
to go to
Cuba
. To
Q
Thank you thank you.
Professor very gentle that.
You are going to have
a king now you are now the rupee. We
have watched Romney have our first
cabinet seventy so I'm not bashing the
women. And I caution you about some of them
may go should I make your last years old.
Six.
Q
Why do you seem to be enjoying you so Oh
yes this is wonderful it's the only thing
I really do enjoy about this. Country
the Fourth of July celebration.
Catherine I've been here for three days
I haven't heard from was anything wrong
wrong I just hope that it hasn't been
necessary for you to say anything to G.W.
. But are you talking
to. Katherine you see
I'm in
a rather delicate position governor of the
territory you know I just hope you haven't
found it necessary to say
anything about. A song. About you
and me. Yeah. Yeah.
You pompous when to. Even think that you
are the only man who's ever tried to play
patty fingers with me who's never tried
to lure me into the moonlight Well no but
I'm
a big girl and I can take care of myself and
my husband know I can assure you as governor
that your reputation is on
time just now get out of my.
Way I sat down at Carnegie.
By the good way.
Best qualified.
Me the you know the company what happened
over what. You smell of being well
naturally I'm drinkin there. How
to build up another well do call.
And. Prakash. Tracked down
just over our character are
a member of the. Or your god is the
whole of my slaves he. Said and I
want it I think told to
Washington we can talk you want
a very crude man well I
guess so but that was
a rub wars like that jarred my
insides. But it was worse that.
Three.
Things.
I. Think.
To
go.
To go.
Look for you I guess so
nothing busted but my pride I
don't even things out for ever for what
that store noise you gave me the other day
Well I'm going to have to show you. I'm.
All right yes.
That's holding if there is a tadpole in
a race the foot of the song is at the
heart of two souls start the endurance.
I mean I know. What is
that called Courage.
You know what Douglas does never use
a thing like that I want you to get on I
don't get out in front and stay out front
I'll be out for us. Oh boy good
boy I remember standing proud
that I got
a man on the good horse. She's
.
Live.
For us this.
Thank you but only time you want to run for
the United Kingdom will finally got his
way but I reckon he's right not his last
war party they will get very far but one
thing still has me puzzled where did they
get the guns I was wondering the same
thing. My kidneys been
bothering me lining. K W.
Oh what an idiotic joke joke you think
that was I joke I shut up if you like
everybody and tell him to send me to
a good. Job I think they've
done yeah. What can I do just
my stuff.
How long G W. A long while I catch She's
been riding herd on you for two years now
I'm
a peaceable man but my father used to say
you raise your voice it doesn't do any good
it's time to raise your hand well I've
been planning to do something but I don't.
But I have another talk with her but to.
Top that we're talking won't do any good.
I kid you see I'm. What's been
happening around here. It's got
a halo all over us it's
a mighty sneaky go one time here during
that great Mr McClintock Oh was it said
only a trollop but just
a man before they were formally engaged
but we are engaged are you all right that
is with your permission. You've
got it all and this is why I
think it's wonderful I guess this is the
only engagement that ever started off the
spanking. I reckon Birnbaum is right.
All right. Lower classes
this is going to be
a great day Oh God Oh no not
a little oh right. Oh yeah oh. Oh
right you can talk has got
run over the top only right.
Maybe. Well not now. Are you insane
I want to talk to you. To wait. To get.
Taken off I'm. Going to tell
me why you. Walked out on me
you remember when you came over from ten.
O'clock. Let us take my collar.
Let the fellow. Like you think you.
Are All Right. You are right.
Well what kind of
a way you. Look
.
Like my.
I.
Let.
Live.
I think.
Make amends.
This is like you said and you start.
To show.
You.
Live.
If. You. Can Fight Oh I don't do you any
good then do you know there isn't any
Murdo years you're going to get your
comeuppance. A little while.
But you may need it. Now get. Sure the.
Old special. Me. Yes.
I'm.
Living in the capital no no more Newport
season. No more dancing at the gov.
No. I beat
a. Three hundred ten
times went out on this.
At some record.
Going.